Guide to the Richard S. Buswell, Photographs of Abandoned Wooden Buildings and Artifacts in Montana
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1986–2017
  - 2013
    - Piano Keys, Summer 2013, 2014 February 1 (Box 4, Folder 294)
    - Rat Tail Noodles, Summer 2013, 2014 January 20 (Box 4, Folder 295)
    - Slate Shingles, Spring 2013, 2014 January 22 (Box 4, Folder 296)
    - Spine and Ribs, Summer 2013, 2014 January 26 (Box 4, Folder 297)
    - Spokes, Summer 2013, 2014 January 2 (Box 4, Folder 298)
    - Tobacco, Summer 2013, 2014 January 24 (Box 4, Folder 299)
  - 2014
    - Abstract No. 1, Summer 2014, 2015 January 2 (Box 5, Folder 300)
    - Beetle Tracks No. 1, Fall 2014, 2015 January 16 (Box 5, Folder 301)
    - Beetle Tracks No. 2, Fall 2014, 2015 January 16 (Box 5, Folder 302)
    - Beetle Tracks No. 3, Fall 2014, 2015 January 18 (Box 5, Folder 303)
    - Bone Series No. 4, Summer 2014, 2015 January 9 (Box 5, Folder 304)
    - Doll Arm, Summer 2014, 2014 December 30 (Box 5, Folder 305)
    - Doll Face No. 2, Summer 2014, 2015 January 6 (Box 5, Folder 306)
    - Doll Face No. 3, Summer 2014, 2015 January 13 (Box 5, Folder 307)
    - Hip Sockets, Summer 2014, 2015 January 4 (Box 5, Folder 308)
    - Knots No. 1, Summer 2014, 2015 January 9 (Box 5, Folder 309)
    - Linoleum, Summer 2014, 2015 January 15 (Box 5, Folder 310)
    - Mushroom, Summer 2014, 2015 January 18 (Box 5, Folder 311)
    - Oven Door, Summer 2014, 2015 January 6 (Box 5, Folder 312)
    - Receipts, Summer 2014, 2015 January 13 (Box 5, Folder 313)
    - Wall Ornament, Summer 2014, 2015 January 2 (Box 5, Folder 314)
  - 2015
    - Cedar Tree, Summer 2015, 2016 January 12 (Box 5, Folder 315)
    - Chinking, Fall 2015, 2016 January 12 (Box 5, Folder 316)
    - Dash Board No. 2, Fall 2015, 2016 January 3 (Box 5, Folder 317)
    - Deer Maxilla No. 2, Summer 2015, 2015 December 30 (Box 5, Folder 318)
    - Enamel Pot, Summer 2015, 2015 December 27 (Box 5, Folder 319)
    - Heater Grate, Summer 2015, 2015 December 27 (Box 5, Folder 320)
    - Homestead Siding, Summer 2015, 2016 January 8 (Box 5, Folder 321)
    - Medallion, Summer 2015, 2016 January 3 (Box 5, Folder 322)
    - Mirror Frame, Summer 2015, 2016 January 14 (Box 5, Folder 323)
    - Missing Brains No. 2, Summer 2015, 2016 January 1 (Box 5, Folder 324)
    - Missing Brains, Summer 2015, 2016 January 1 (Box 5, Folder 325)
    - Shoes, Summer 2015, 2016 January 10 (Box 5, Folder 326)
    - Sunflower, Summer 2015, 2016 January 18 (Box 5, Folder 327)
    - Tipi Hide, Summer 2015, 2016 January 10 (Box 5, Folder 328)
  - 2016
    - Bark, Fall 2016, 2017 January 23 (Box 5, Folder 329)
    - Barn Ceiling, Summer 2016, 2017 January 3 (Box 5, Folder 330)
    - Birch Pattern, Fall 2016, 2017 January 21 (Box 5, Folder 331)
    - Bird Wings, Summer 2016, 2017 January 8 (Box 5, Folder 332)
    - Blizzard, Late Winter 2016, 2017 January 10 (Box 5, Folder 333)
    - Bone Series No. 5, Summer 2016, 2017 January 6 (Box 5, Folder 334)
    - Cabin Chinking, Summer 2016, 2017 January 19 (Box 5, Folder 335)
    - Car Rust, Summer 2016, 2017 January 10 (Box 5, Folder 336)
    - Chair Back No. 2, Summer 2016, 2017 January 21 (Box 5, Folder 337)
    - Clay Mold, Summer 2016, 2017 January 6 (Box 5, Folder 338)
    - Coffee Can No. 2, Summer 2016, 2017 January 8 (Box 5, Folder 339)
    - Door Pattern, Summer 2016, 2017 January 3 (Box 5, Folder 340)
    - Driftwood, Summer 2016, 2017 January 26 (Box 5, Folder 341)
    - Feathers No. 2, Summer 2016, 2017 January 19 (Box 5, Folder 342)
    - Mushroom Gills, Fall 2016, 2017 January 15 (Box 5, Folder 343)
    - Peas, Summer 2016, 2017 January 13 (Box 5, Folder 344)
    - Thistle, Summer 2016, 2017 January 13 (Box 5, Folder 345)
    - Vertebral Disk, Summer 2016, 2017 January 15 (Box 5, Folder 346)